听着 我最后一次告诉你 我不在乎电脑上登记了什么
Listen, you know what? Sir, for the last time, I don't care what the computer says.
我们没有从房间冰箱拿走一包糖果
We did not take a bag of Meshugga Nuts from the minibar.
我们没有看"热心助人的医生"
And we did not watch Dr. Do-Me-A-Little.
- 嗨   - 噢
- Hey.     - Oh.
- 乔伊 昨晚你到过我们房间   - 没有
- Joey, were you in our room last night?     - No.
他们说电影片名不会出现在帐单上
I was told the name of the movie would not appear on the bill.
- 嗨 我们要退掉新房了   - 没错 我不再是新娘了
- Hi, we're checking out of the bridal suite. - That's right, I'm no longer a bride.
我永远都当不了新娘 现在我只是某人的太太
I'll never be a bride again. Now I'm just someone's wife.
现在我是全世界最快乐的男人
And I'm the happiest guy in the world.
甜心 别难过 我们还是有很光明的未来
Come on, honey. Don't be upset. We have so much to look forward to.
对
Yeah, right.
- 我们还要去度蜜月   - 那是星期四的事
- The honeymoon.     - That's not till Thursday.
- 还有婚纱照   - 那得等上好几个星期
- The wedding pictures.     - Those won't be ready weeks.
但婚宴上用即可拍 拍的照片马上可以洗好
Not the disposable cameras from the tables.
没错 我就知道我嫁给你是有原因的
That's true! I knew I married you for a reason!
听着 我拿照片去洗 你先回家吧
I'll tell you what. I will go get them developed, and you can go home.
- 什么 你拍了什么   - 没什么 一定很精彩
- What? What did you take a picture of?     - Nothing. It was something.
即可拍在罗斯那里 他还没有退房吗
Okay, Ross has the cameras. Is he checked out yet?
你在开玩笑吗 退房时间是中午
Are you joking? Checkout is not till noon.
- 他还有整整11分钟呢   - 所以呢
- And he has a good 11 minutes left.     - So?
罗斯从来不会提早退房
So Ross has never checked out of a room a minute before he had to.
我们在交往的时候
Yeah, one time when we were dating...
有一次延后退房 他非常兴奋 那是我们最棒的性经验
...we got a late checkout, he got so excited, it was the best sex we ever had.
直到他最后大叫着"拉迪森旅馆"
Until he screamed out "Radisson" at the end.
好吧 我去找罗斯拿照相机 然后把底片拿去洗
Okay, I'm gonna get Ross, get the cameras, and get them developed.
乔伊 你32岁了
Thirty-two, Joe. You're 32!
- 这是你的帐单   - 谢谢
- Here's a copy of your bill.     - Oh, thanks.
香槟 草莓…
Champagne, strawberries...
天啊 我不敢相信 钱德在我们的新婚之夜看黄色电影
Oh, my God! I can't believe Chandler ordered porn on our wedding night.
对 那真的很惨
Yeah, that's sad.
糖果
Meshugga Nut?
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
- 嗨   - 嗨
- Hi.     - Hi.
肥皂 洗发精 你真的要拿这些东西
Soaps, shampoos. Are you really taking all this stuff?
- 为什么不行 这全包含在房费里 - 对 但你不需要…
- Why not? It's built into the price of the room.     - Yeah, but you don't need...
-  这是什么   - 针线包
- What is this?     - Thread.
答对了
Score!
- 即可拍在哪里   - 什么即可拍
- Where are the disposable cameras?     - What disposable cameras?
昨晚我把它们交给你
Last night I asked you to take them.
- 才没有   - 就是有 记得吗 在切蛋糕前我说…
- No, you didn't.     - Yes, before we cut the cake, I said...
对 你问我能不能帮你一个忙
Yeah, you came up to me and asked me for a favor.
这时墨瑞叔叔走过来交给你一张支票
And then my Uncle Murray came up to you and handed you a check.
然后你说"它为什么叫支票" "为什么不叫南斯拉夫人"
Then you said, "Why do they call it a check? Why not a Yugoslavian?"
- 对 然后你就那么做   - 所以即可拍不在你手上
- Yeah, then you did that.     - So you don't have the cameras?
- 没错 抱歉   - 什么
- No, sorry.     - So what? What?
相机不见了 摩妮卡会气疯的
They're gone? Monica's gonna freak!
我相信它们应该就在某个地方
'm sure they're here somewhere.
我帮你找
I'll help you look for them.
- 太棒了   - 再等三分钟
- Great.     - In three minutes.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey     - Hey.
你要不管钱德 自己先拆礼物
Are you gonna open the presents without Chandler?
不 我只是…
No.
它们在呼唤我
They're calling out to me.
这个小家伙甚至爬到我的膝盖上
This little guy even crawled up in my lap.
钱德不会介意我拆开一样礼物
Come on, Chandler wouldn't mind if I opened just one present.
你觉得它是什么
What do you think it is?
是一面小镜子 只要你照它 你会发现自己变成了老太婆
A mirror that when you look into it, you see yourself as an old woman.
是一个迷你盐罐
A tiny salt shaker!
天啊 是用来装迷你盐的
Oh, my God, for tiny salt!
好吧 那真的很好玩
Oh, wow! Okay, that was fun.
很好玩
Oh, yeah.
我会等钱德再一起拆开其他礼物
I'm just gonna wait for Chandler to open up the rest of them.
- 好   - 喔
- Okay.     - Whoo!
但这只是调味瓶组的一部分
Although, you know, this is part of a salt-and-pepper set.
或许它只算半项礼物 你觉得呢
So I guess it may just count as half a present. What do you think?
我猜如果它是一套 再拆开一样也没关系 或许是这个
Well, I guess it's okay to open one more if it's part of a set. It's probably this one.
或是这个
Or this one!
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
你好吗 会害喜吗
How you feeling? Got any morning sickness?
男生们还不知道吧
Shh! The guys don't know yet, do they?
不 乔伊跟罗斯什么都不知道 钱德还认为是菲比怀孕了
No. Joey and Ross don't know anything, and Chandler thinks Phoebe's pregnant.
没错 钱德还是以为我怀孕了
That's right. Chandler does still think I'm pregnant.
他没有问我感觉如何 也没有帮我提袋子
He hasn't asked me how I'm feeling, or offered to carry my bags.
我为跟他在一起的女人觉得难过
I feel bad for the woman who ends up with him.
我当然是指在你之后的女人
After you, of course.
别担心 你只需要再假装怀孕几小时
Don't worry. I promise that you will only have to be pregnant a few more hours.
因为今天我要告诉孩子的爸
I'm going to tell the father today.
他就住在这栋公寓吗 是一楼那个高个儿吗
Is it someone in this building? That tall guy from the first floor?
- 才不是   - 什么 我觉得他很可爱
- Eww! No!     - What? I think he's cute.
- 那么你可以去怀他的孩子   - 相信我 我正在努力
- Well, then you have his baby.     - Believe me, I'm trying.
这真的好奇怪 你今天要告诉这个男人…
Wow. It's so weird. You're gonna tell this guy today...
他不知道会发生什么事
...and he has no idea what's gonna happen.
对 你要敲敲他的门 然后永远改变他的一生
Yeah. You're just gonna knock on his door and change his life forever.
你就像艾德·麦马汉 只不过手上没有拿大额支票
You're like Ed McMahon, except without the big check.
也没有原始的性吸引力
Or the raw sexual magnetism.
- 对 我想那的确是个大消息 - 大消息 那是超级大消息
- Yeah, I guess it is pretty big news.     - Pretty big? It's huge!
天啊 这个男人什么都不知道 他走在街上心想
God, this guy doesn't have a clue. He's walking around thinking:
"我跟瑞秋·葛林做爱 太帅了"
"I had sex with Rachel Green. I rock!"
然后 砰 他当了爸爸 一切都不一样了
Then, bam! He's a father, everything's different.
除非他真的想当爸爸 我不会对他提出任何要求
Well, it's only different if he wants it to be. I'm not gonna ask him for anything.
他还是得做出重大的决定 现在他边走边想
Then he still has this huge decision to make. Now he's thinking:
"我要当爸爸吗" 然后 砰
"Do I want to be a dad?" Then, bam!
- 这次怎么了   - 我不知道 他可能是撞上巴士了
- What was that "bam"?     - I don't know. He's hit by a bus.
- 嗨   - 嘿
- Hi.     - Hey.
乔伊 如果跟你上床的女人说她怀孕了 你会怎么办
Joey, what would you do if someone you slept with told you she was pregnant?
谁打电话到这里来
Who called here?
她听起来像金发美女吗 她有口音吗 我得去打个电话
Did she sound blond? Any accent? I gotta make a call.
我不该走进那家太阳眼镜专卖店的
Should have never walked into that Sunglass Hut!
乔伊…不是你 你没有让任何人怀孕
Oh, Joey! Joey! It's not you! You didn't get anyone pregnant.
你为什么要那样子吓我 发生了什么事
Why would you scare me like that? What the hell's going on?
有人怀孕了吗
Is somebody pregnant?
对 我怀孕了
Oh, yeah! That's me.
天啊 菲比 你要生孩子了
Oh, my God, Pheebs! You're gonna have a baby?
对
Yes, I am.
天啊 我要生孩子了
Oh, my God, I'm gonna have a baby!
- 等一下 孩子的爸是谁   - 你不认识他
- Wait, who's the father?     - You don't know him.
那不重要 他不希望跟我或孩子扯上关系
He wants nothing to do with me or the baby.
这家伙是谁 因为我要把他揪出来痛扁他一顿
Who is this guy? Who is he? Because I'll track him down and kick his ass!
- 大卫·林恩   - 大卫·林恩
- David Linn.     - David Linn!
大卫·林恩 大卫·林恩
David Linn! David Linn!
- 谁是大卫·林恩   - 我在健身房认识的人 他很讨厌
- Who's David Linn?     - Some guy from my gym. A little annoying.
- 钱德   - 嘿 你找到即可拍了吗
- Chandler?     - Hey. Did you find the cameras?
没有 你呢
No. Did you?
我找到了 那就是我躲在桌下的原因 我想要庆祝
Yes, that's why I'm under the table. Celebrating.
我去失物中心
I checked in the lost and found.
问过经理 没有人捡到即可拍
I talked to the manager. No one's turned them in.
太棒了 今天只有那些即可拍能让摩妮卡高兴起来
Great. Those cameras were the only thing that will cheer Monica up.
她真的很沮丧
She's depressed.
你们才刚刚结婚 她为什么会沮丧
You guys just got married. Why is she so depressed?
我没有力气问她那个问题
All my energy is going into not asking that question.
- 我不敢相信我搞砸了  - 我很遗憾 兄弟
- I can't believe I screwed this up!     - I'm sorry, man.
我有个点子 你们在这个宴会厅请客
Here's a thought. This is the same ballroom.
这里有乐队 等一下会有很多人盛装前来
There's a band. There's gonna be plenty of dressed up people.
你建议我们可以丢下问题不管
Are you suggesting we dance our troubles away?
不 我是说我们到礼品店买一些即可拍
No, we buy more of these at the gift shop,
再换上礼服 拍几张照片
throw our tuxes on and take a few pictures.
我们只要 不拍到任何人的脸就好
All have to do is make sure not to get people's faces.
你是认真的吗
Are you serious?
我想到在家等你的新娘
I'm just thinking about your new bride.
你想在你们共度一生的第一天就让她失望吗
Okay? Do you really want to start your life together by letting her down?
你真的要给我关于婚姻的建议
Marriage advice? Really?
我是在告诉你 这看起来很像你的婚宴
I'm telling you, this looks exactly like your wedding.
- 这些花都一样吧   - 我不知道 花是摩妮卡挑的
- Aren't these the same flowers?     - I don't know. Monica picked them.
- 椅子呢   - 也是她
- The chairs?     - Those too.
- 布置呢   - 她挑的
- The place settings?     - Her.
- 你做了什么   - 我负责看好照相机
- What did you do?     - I was in charge of the cameras.
- 礼品店   - 嗯
- Gift shop?     - Mm.
嗨
Hey.
- 你说了吗   - 还没有
- Did you do it yet?     - Not yet.
那么你在这里做什么  你真的要说吗
Then what are you doing here? Are you about to do it?
- 是阿甘吗 - 不是…
- Is it Gunther?     - No...
- 不是阿甘   - 谢天谢地 还好宝宝不会有他的头发
- It's not Gunther!     - Thank God. That hair on a baby?
孩子的爸不在这里 好吗
The father is not here, okay?
我还没有告诉他 我想现在我没办法告诉他
I haven't told him, and I don't think I can now.
- 为什么   - 让我想想
- Why not?     - Now let me think.
我在街上边走边想
I was walking down the street, thinking,
"我要告诉孩子的爸" 然后 砰
"I'm gonna tell the father today." And then, bam!
你撞到了巴士
Bus?
不 是你 你吓了我一跳 你一直在提醒我这件事有多大
No, you! You freaked me out. You kept saying how huge this all is.
- 但它的确是件大事   - 我知道
- But it is huge.     - I know.
我只是在想它对我来说有多重要
But I was just thinking about how huge it was for me.
我根本不知道这对孩子的爸来说有多重要
I didn't go to how huge this is gonna be for the father.
你想太多了
You're thinking about this way too much.
告诉他把事情做个了断
Just tell him and get it over with.
它就像撕掉OK绷一样 越快越不痛 你看
It's like ripping off this Band-Aid, quick and painless. Watch.
喔 天杀的…
Oh, mother of...!
看吧
See?
- 喔 我们要拆礼物了吗   - 不 我根本不该拆开礼物的
- Ooh. Are we opening presents?     - No. I shouldn't have even opened these.
乔伊 我控制不了自己
Joey, I am out of control!
你得帮我一个忙
You have to do me a favor.
不论我说什么 不论我做什么
No matter what I say, no matter what I do,
拜托 不要让我再拆开任何礼物
please do not let me open another present.
- 好吗   - 好
- Okay?     - Okay.
- 再给我一个礼物   - 好
- Give me one more.     - Okay.
- 嗨   - 很好 你来了 菲比 听我说…
- Hey.     - Oh, good. You're here. Pheebs? Listen...
- 坐下 我要告诉你一件事   - 好吧
- Sit down, I got something I want to say.     - All right.
嗯
Um...
外面的世界很可怕 特别是对单亲妈妈来说
It's a scary world out there, especially for a single mom.
我一直觉得我跟你之间很特别
Now, I always felt that you and I have a special bond.
所以…
So...
菲比·布非 你愿意嫁给我吗
So, Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
- 乔伊   - 我愿意嫁给你
- Joey!     - Oh, yeah, I'll marry you.
- 你不能嫁给他 - 小姐 你结过婚了 这次轮到我
- You can't marry him!     - Hey, lady, your day's over, it's my turn.
- 菲比   - 她为什么不能嫁给我
- Phoebe!     - What? Why can't she marry me?
我可以 我也愿意
I can and I will.
她没有怀孕 是瑞秋怀孕了 好吗
She's not pregnant. It's Rachel. Rachel's the one who's pregnant, okay.
- 天啊   - 嘿
- Oh, my God!     - Hey.
菲比 九个月后你生不出孩子 他会发现的
He'd notice when you didn't have a baby in nine months!
他是乔伊
It's Joey!
我爱你
I love you.
等一下 我不敢相信 瑞秋怀孕了
I can't believe it! Rachel's pregnant?
- 对   - 孩子的爸是谁
- Yeah.     - Who's the father?
我们不知道
We don't know.
- 不知道是不是那个家伙   - 有个家伙
- I wonder if it's that dude.     - There's a dude?
- 对   - 是谁呢
- Yeah.     - Who is it?
一个月前这家伙跟瑞秋共度春宵 我没有看到他 但是…
A month ago this guy spent the night. I didn't see who it was, but...
他把故事说完了吗
Was that story over?
那个家伙留下这个
The guy left this.
天啊 我知道孩子的爸是谁
Oh, my God! I know who the father is.
说故事的人得把故事说完
People have got to finish their stories.
- 对不起 你能帮我们拍照吗   - 没问题
- Excuse me. Could you take a picture of us?     - Oh. Of course.
- 你能帮我们照一张吗   - 好 没问题
- Would you take one of us?     - Uh. Yeah, sure.
喀
Click.
- 我没有听到快门声   - 我听到了
- It didn't click.     - I heard it.
- 但闪光灯没亮   - 你为什么不帮我们拍照
- But there was no flash.     - Why won't you take our picture?
好 我会帮你们拍照
Yeah, I'll take your picture.
- 你的手指挡到镜头了  - 你是安瑟·亚当斯吗 快滚吧
- Your finger was covering the lens.    - Who are you, Ansel Adams? Get out of here!
（中央咖啡厅）
听着 我真的很难过 之前我吓坏你了…
Look, I feel really bad about how I freaked you out before...
所以我请孩子的爸到里面等你 你可以告诉他事实
...so I called the father and asked him to meet you here. Go!
什么 等一下 你怎么知道孩子的爸是谁
What? Wait a minute. How do you even know who the father is?
或许有时候我会装傻…
I may play the fool at times...
但事实上我是个永不放弃的金发美女
...but I'm more than a pretty blond with an ass that won't quit.
我相信这是孩子爸的衣服…
I believe this belongs to the father of your baby.
天啊
Oh, God.
- 他就在里面   - 啊哈
- Oh. He's in there right now?     - Uh-huh.
你可以转身离开或是长痛不如短痛
You can turn around, or you can go in there and rip the Band-Aid off.
你打算怎么做
What do you wanna do?
- 我们把事情做个了断吧   - 你确定
- Let's rip.     - Really? Are you sure?
- 菲比   - 好吧 抱歉
- Phoebe!     - Okay. Sorry. Yeah.
嘿 瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
你为什么不到台上呢 我要拍张你说话时的照片
Go on-stage. I'll get a picture of you doing the speech.
好
Okay. Okay.
1995年别克·李萨布利的车主请跟柜台联络
Will the owner of a 1995 Buick LeSabre please see the front desk?
你的车就要被拖走了
Your car is about to be towed.
那是我的车
That's my car!
- 1995年的李萨布利   - 对
- A '95 LeSabre?     - Yes.
- 绿色的李萨布利   - 对
- A green LeSabre?     - Yes!
- 抱歉 我是说蓝色的李萨布利 - 对 我的车是蓝绿色的
- I'm sorry, I meant blue.     - Yes, green-blue.
那就快去把它移开吧
Well, go. Go move it!
- 好了 准备要拍最后一张照片了吗   - 对
- Okay. Ready for the last picture?     - Yeah.
拍完 马上就跑
Get ready to run.
恭喜
Congratulations on your wedding.
这是怎么一回事
So, what's this about?
瑞秋有事要告诉你
Rachel has something that she wants to tell you.
我相信这是你的红毛衣
And I believe that this is your red sweater.
不 这才是我的红毛衣
No, this is my red sweater.
喔 糟糕
Oh, no.
有人要喝咖啡吗
Could I get anyone a coffee?
或是毒药 没有吗 只有我要 好吧
Or poison? No? Just for me? Okay.
发生了什么事 瑞秋
What's going on?
没事 菲比弄错了
Nothing. Phoebe kind of made a mistake.
但你的确常穿那件毛衣 你在做什么冒险的事吗
But you do wear that sweater a lot. Are you involved in some kind of dare?
事实上我很高兴能接到菲比的电话
I'm actually glad Phoebe called.
我知道我们会分手是因为你觉得我太幼雅
I know we broke up because you thought I wasn't mature enough...
但我已经长大了 我想我们应该复合
...but I've really grown up. And I think we should get back together.
时机很不对
It's just not the right time.
- 时机非常恰当   - 好吧
- It is the right time.     - Okay.
- 我做了万全的准备   - 泰格
- I'm ready for more.     - Tag.
来吧 瑞秋 我们可以再试一次
Come on, Rach. Let's give it another try.
- 我怀孕了   - 噢
- I'm having a baby.     - Oh.
- 你可以走了   - 谢谢
- You can go.     - Thank you.
我不知道礼物怎么会是打开的
I don't know how any of these got opened!
- 你拆开了所有的礼物   - 我知道 我是个可怕的人
- You opened them all?     - I know, I am a terrible person.
钱德永远都不会再信任我任何事了
Chandler's never gonna trust me with anything ever again.
- 你拆开了我爸妈的礼物   - 对 那是什么
- Hey! You got my parents' gift.     - Yeah. What is that?
应该是跟意大利腊肠有关的东西
I don't know. I think it does something to salami.
- 嘿 情况如何   - 泰格怎么说
- Hey. How'd it go?     - Yeah. What did Tag say?
泰格不是孩子的爸 乔伊知道了
Tag is not the father. And Joey knows now?
我知道了 瑞秋 我为你感到高兴
I do, Rach. I do. And I'm so happy for you.
你没有试着要解开我的胸罩
Oh. Wow, you didn't even try to unhook my bra.
你要告诉孩子的爸吗
So are you ever gonna tell whoever it is?
我会的 只是今晚我不想那么做
I will, I'm just not up for it tonight.
不论这家伙说什么 你不会独自面对这一切
Hey, Rach, listen. No matter what he says, you're not gonna be alone.
- 是吗   - 不
- I'm not?     - No.
听着…
Listen, I, uh...
外面的世界很可怕 特别是对单亲妈妈来说
It's a scary world out there, especially for a single mom.
啊
Aww.
我一直觉得我跟你之间很特别
I've always felt like you and I have this special bond.
- 瑞秋·葛林 你愿意嫁给我吗   - 什么
- Rachel Green, will you marry me?     - What?
- 什么   - 什么
- What?     - What?!
- 菲比 把戒指还给我 - 不要
- Pheebs, give me the ring back.     - No!
乔伊 你真的很体贴
Joey, you're so sweet. You are so, so sweet, honey.
但我不要一个丈夫
But I'm not looking for a husband.
我了解
I understand.
对不起 我想去躺一下
Now if you'll excuse me, I'm going to go and lie down.
我不能说我不心痛
I can't say that didn't hurt.
- 但我会原谅你 乔伊·崔比亚尼   - 听着 我只是说
- But I'll take you back, Joey Tribbiani.     - Year,please lisen about that, I...
- 意大利腊肠用具   - 来吧
- Ohh, a Salami Buddy!     - There you go!
- 我们回来了   - 太棒了
- We're back!     - Great.
我们待在厨房吧 待在厨房就好了
We're hanging in the kitchen. Let's stay in the kitchen.
- 现在是看照片时间   - 你一定会喜欢的
- It's picture time.     - You're gonna love these.
这是罗斯的照片
Here's a picture of Ross.
那是我
And that's me.
我跟罗斯
And that's me and Ross.
这是我们第一次以新婚夫妻身份接吻的照片
Aww. And here's our first kiss as a married couple.
那张照片真的很棒
Wow. That is a great picture.
对 真的太有趣了 因为我在我们的行李里找到即可拍
Yeah. And interesting, because I found the cameras in one of our bags.
我没想到会这样
Huh. Didn't see that coming.
好 这不是我们第一次接吻的照片…
Okay, so this isn't the picture of our first kiss...
但它的确是我跟这位女士第一次接吻的照片
...but it is a picture of my first kiss with this lady.
从你脸上的表情看来 我相信你会记得 所以我不必…
Which, by the look on your face, I'm sure you'll remember, so there's no need...
我会拿真的底片去洗
I'll take the real pictures to them developed.
- 好主意   - 好
- That'd be a good idea.     - Okay.
你不管我自己拆开所有礼物 我们说好要一起拆的
You opened all the presents without me? We were gonna do that together.
你吻了另一个女人
You kissed another woman?
- 我们扯平了   - 好吧
- Call it even?     - Okay.
- 我要把花插到花瓶里   - 你偷走了那个婚礼的花
- Well, I'm gonna go get these in some water.   - You stole those from that wedding?
不 这是饭店大厅的花 他们以为能收我黄色电影…
No, the hotel lobby. They think they can charge me for some dirty movie
还有一袋糖果的钱 我一定要讨回公道
and a bag of Meshugga Nuts they got another thing coming!
嘿 我的毛衣
Hey, my sweater!
我找这件毛衣找了一个月
I've been looking for this for like a month.
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
- 你好吗   - 我很好 好久不见
- Hey, how you doing?     - Good. Long time no see.
- 我喜欢你的毛衣   - 我也是
- Like your sweater.     - Oh. Hey. Right back at you.
- 瑞秋的事真的太疯狂了   - 她一直都疯疯癫癫的
- It's crazy about Rachel.     - Yeah. Well, she's one crazy lady.
- 到底是谁的呢   - 我不知道 应该是某个意大利人吧
- So whose is it?     - Um, I don't know, some Italian guy.
少来了 看你自己的标签 后会有期
Come on, read your own label. See you later.
- 好   - 他真是奇怪
- Okay.     - He is so weird.